https://timberframemag.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy - Timber Frame Homes
Skip to content828-524-8662info@timberframepros.comMon-Thur  9:00-3:00   Fri   By Appointment FacebookPinterestTwitterTimber Frame HomesTimber Frame Design and Build HomeHome PlansCustom Home DesignPlans up to 2100 Square FeetPlans 2100 – 3000 Square FeetPlans 3100 Square Feet and UpOne Bedroom PlansTwo Bedroom Plans3 – 4 – & More BedroomsWhy Timber Frame?Planning A Timber Frame HomeGreen BuildingCraftsmanship – A Timber Frame TraditionAdvantages of Timber Frame HomesEnergy EfficiencyThe ProcessTimber Frame Design ServicesTimber Frame Packages – What’s Included?Home Design WorkbookFeatured HomeGalleryFAQSWarrantyPrivacy PolicyContact UsTimber Frame Home Design WorkbookSearch: Search
HomeHome PlansCustom Home DesignPlans up to 2100 Square FeetPlans 2100 – 3000 Square FeetPlans 3100 Square Feet and UpOne Bedroom PlansTwo Bedroom Plans3 – 4 – & More BedroomsWhy Timber Frame?Planning A Timber Frame HomeGreen BuildingCraftsmanship – A Timber Frame TraditionAdvantages of Timber Frame HomesEnergy EfficiencyThe ProcessTimber Frame Design ServicesTimber Frame Packages – What’s Included?Home Design WorkbookFeatured HomeGalleryFAQSWarrantyPrivacy PolicyContact UsTimber Frame Home Design WorkbookPrivacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyIt is the policy of Timber Frame Homes, Inc. not to utilize online inquiry forms to collect information. Inquiries made by our customers concerning our timber frames are for our sole use.  Timber Frame Homes, Inc. never uses or shares your personal information with any third parties.To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information you choose to share with us.Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at (828) 524-8662 or email bonnie@timberframepros.com Share this page Share on FacebookShare on Facebook TweetShare on Twitter Pin itShare on PinterestContact Us37 Phillips StreetFranklin, NC 28734.828-524-8662info@timberframepros.com.Hours:Mon-Thur: 9 AM – 3 PMFri By Appointment © Timber Frame Homes Inc. 2019Previously used menu 3 Go to Top
